{
    "Songs": {
        "Like Melodies": {
            "Song": {
                "Line01": {
                    "Question": "Wie Melodien zieht es",
                    "Answer": "Thoughts, like melodies,"
                }, "Line02": {
                    "Question": "Mir leise durch den Sinn,",
                    "Answer": "Steal softly through my mind,"
                }, "Line03": {
                    "Question": "Wie Frühlingsblumen blüht es",
                    "Answer": "Like spring flowers they blossom"
                }, "Line04": {
                    "Question": "Und schwebt wie Duft dahin.",
                    "Answer": "And drift away like fragrance."
                }, "Line05": {
                    "Question": "Doch kommt das Wort und faßt es",
                    "Answer": "Yet when words come and capture them"
                }, "Line06": {
                    "Question": "Und führt es vor das Aug’,",
                    "Answer": "And bring them before my eyes,"
                }, "Line07": {
                    "Question": "Wie Nebelgrau erblaßt es",
                    "Answer": "They turn pale like grey mist"
                }, "Line08": {
                    "Question": "Und schwindet wie ein Hauch.",
                    "Answer": "And vanish like a breath."
                }, "Line09": {
                    "Question": "Und dennoch ruht im Reime",
                    "Answer": "Yet surely in rhyme"
                }, "Line10": {
                    "Question": "Verborgen wohl ein Duft,",
                    "Answer": "A fragrance lies hidden,"
                }, "Line11": {
                    "Question": "Den mild aus stillem Keime",
                    "Answer": "Summoned by moist eyes"
                }, "Line12": {
                    "Question": "Ein feuchtes Auge ruft.",
                    "Answer": "From the silent seed."
                }
            }
        }, "Tears fall in my heart": {
            "Song": {
                "Line01": {
                    "Question": "Il pleure dans mon cœur",
                    "Answer": "The tears fall in my soul"
                }, "Line02": {
                    "Question": "Comme il pleut sur la ville",
                    "Answer": "As the rain on the town"
                }, "Line03": {
                    "Question": "Quelle est cette langueur",
                    "Answer": "Wherefore creeps this deep dole/torpor"
                }, "Line04": {
                    "Question": "Qui pénètre mon cœur",
                    "Answer": "Who penetrates my soul"
                }, "Line05": {
                    "Question": "Ô bruit doux de la pluie",
                    "Answer": "Oh sound sweet of the rain"
                }, "Line06": {
                    "Question": "Par terre et sur les toits!",
                    "Answer": "On the ground and on the rooftops"
                }, "Line07": {
                    "Question": "Pour un cœur qui s’ennuie",
                    "Answer": "For a heart that bored"
                }, "Line08": {
                    "Question": "Ô le bruit de la pluie!",
                    "Answer": "Oh the sound of the rain"
                }, "Line09": {
                    "Question": "Il pleure sans raison",
                    "Answer": "The rain (is) without reason/purpose"
                }, "Line10": {
                    "Question": "Dans ce cœur qui s’écœure.",
                    "Answer": "In this soul who is disgusted"
                }, "Line11": {
                    "Question": "Quoi! nulle trahison",
                    "Answer": "What! No treason"
                }, "Line12": {
                    "Question": "Ce deuil est sans raison.",
                    "Answer": "The mourning is without reason."
                }, "Line13": {
                    "Question": "C’est bien la pire peine",
                    "Answer": "It is indeed the worst pain"
                }, "Line13": {
                    "Question": "Dene savoir pour quoi",
                    "Answer": "Not to know for why"
                }, "Line15": {
                    "Question": "Sans amour et sans haine,",
                    "Answer": "Without love and without hate"
                }, "Line16": {
                    "Question": "Mon cœur a tant de peine.",
                    "Answer": "My heart has so much of pain"
                }
            }
        }, "Dedication": {
            "Song": {
                "Line01": {
                    "Question": "Du meine Seele, du mein Herz,",
                    "Answer": "You my soul you my heart"
                }, "Line02": {
                    "Question": "Du meine Wonn’, o du mein Schmerz,",
                    "Answer": "You my soul you my heart"
                }, "Line03": {
                    "Question": "Du meine Welt, in der ich lebe,",
                    "Answer": "You my world in which I live"
                }, "Line04": {
                    "Question": "Mein Himmel du, darein ich schwebe,",
                    "Answer": "My heaven you, in it I fly (levitate/float),"
                }, "Line05": {
                    "Question": "O du mein Grab, in das hinab",
                    "Answer": "O you my grave in the down"
                }, "Line06": {
                    "Question": "Ich ewig meinen Kummer gab!",
                    "Answer": "My eternal believe/think grief (I) give."
                }, "Line07": {
                    "Question": "Du bist die Ruh, du bist der Frieden,",
                    "Answer": "You are the repose, you are the peace,"
                }, "Line08": {
                    "Question": "Du bist vom Himmel mir beschieden.",
                    "Answer": "You are from heaven I've decided"
                }, "Line09": {
                    "Question": "Dass du mich liebst, macht mich mir wert,",
                    "Answer": "That you want (my) love, makes myself me value"
                }, "Line10": {
                    "Question": "Dein Blick hat mich vor mir verklärt,",
                    "Answer": "Your eyes got me before I transfigured"
                }, "Line11": {
                    "Question": "Du hebst mich liebend über mich,",
                    "Answer": "You raise me lovingly above myself"
                }, "Line12": {
                    "Question": "Mein guter Geist, mein bess’res Ich!",
                    "Answer": "My better angel/spirit my better self"
                }
            }
        }
    }
}
